{
    "id": "a1b25773aad04b8e80e7eb8700ee2c65",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .............................. my cell phone yesterday.",
            "description": "When you lose something, you are deprived of it.",
            "answers": [
                "missed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At least 10 people ……………………. their lives in the accident.",
            "description": "When you lose something, you suffer the loss of it.",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "missed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................ the flight because I overslept.",
            "description": "When you miss something, you fail to access it.",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "missed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We played well yet we ……………………. the match.",
            "description": "When you lose the game, you are defeated.",
            "answers": [
                "missed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………. climbers have been found.",
            "description": "Missing climbers means lost climbers.",
            "answers": [
                "missing",
                "losing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although they searched the entire neighborhood, they couldn’t find the ……………………… cat.",
            "description": "The missing cat is the lost cat. ",
            "answers": [
                "missing",
                "lost",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The shooter ………………………. the target.",
            "description": "Miss can mean fail to hit.",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "missed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. the show because I couldn’t leave work on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "missed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't .................................. any more deadlines.",
            "description": "Miss can mean fail to meet",
            "answers": [
                "miss",
                "lose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I lost the phone yesterday, I didn’t …………………….. it until this morning.",
            "description": "Miss can mean notice the loss or absence of",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "miss"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Now that dad is away for work, I ……………………….. him badly.",
            "description": "When you miss somebody you long for them.",
            "answers": [
                "miss",
                "lose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………….. the project because of some issues with the client.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "missed",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}